faves.com 2008-06-24

# Faves: Privacy Policy

### Faves Privacy Policy

Faves provides an online application that helps people find and discover things by leveraging the power of their social networks. To accomplish this, registered users of the Faves software and/or website (“Users”) may create shared information. Users may also send email invitation requests to other Users.   For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, each such other User is a “Friend” and is defined as someone you have sent a request to or explicitly invited to share information with you. To fulfill the purpose of our website, we need to display a limited amount of personal information so that Users are able to evaluate the trustworthiness of particular pieces of information, each a Fave, and the possible reviews, ratings, or opinions expressed therein. Each Fave created by a User via Faves’ technology has the ability to be made private and to therefore be made available solely to the authoring User.

#### Information We Collect

By using the Faves software and/or website you explicitly agree to permit the collection and use of your personal information by Faves as outlined below in this Privacy Policy.

Faves collects User submitted account information such as name and email address to identify you and send you notifications related to your use of the Faves software. Faves also collects User submitted location information such as city, state or zip code, and User submitted comments and ratings about the various Fave which you create. All such User submitted data is collected and stored at Faves’ or its agent’s facilities for possible aggregation, sale and/or provision to third parties. If such aggregated data is sold, no personally identifying information about any User, such as name or email, will be supplied to the third party.

Additionally, some information we collect is not explicitly submitted by the User. For instance, we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested and referring URLs and timestamp. This information helps us diagnose problems with our servers, administer support, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you.

#### How We Use Your Information

Information such as your full name or email address may be shown to your Buddies or other Users primarily in conjunction with Faves you have contributed and designated as being available for viewing by the general public. If you have designated another User as a Friend they can also see your name or email address in their list of Buddies.

Your full name and email address may also be used when you send an email notification to another User, such as in a request for faving activity, in an invitation, when sharing a Fave, or when forwarding a request. Faves may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site. You can opt out of receiving such communications by emailing [removeme@faves.com](mailto:removeme@faves.com). Additionally, we may use your email address to contact you on behalf of your Buddies (such as when a Friend asks for a Fave).

#### Transfer of Information

Other than as specified in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless we believe we are required to do so by law or have a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) enforce the Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (d) respond to user support requests, or (e) protect the rights or property of Faves, its Users or the public.

User's personal information collected by Faves may be stored and processed in the United States or in any other country in which Faves or its agents maintain facilities. By using Faves’ software and/or website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Faves reserves the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Faves, such as an acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Faves will notify you before information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Like most websites, Faves requires cookies to function properly. Cookies are small data files that are sent to and reside on a User's computer and identify you as a unique User. This identification helps us better understand our user base, refine our software and website and simplify our User’s experiences. We believe our cookies improve the quality of our services, however, you can reset your browser so that it refuses all cookies, or notifies you when a cookie is being sent.

#### Controlling Your Personal Information

As a Faves User, you can modify your personal information at any time by accessing the "My Account " section of the website. You can terminate your account at any time by emailing [admin@faves.com](mailto:admin@faves.com). We typically deactivate accounts within two business days of such requests. You should be aware, however, that residual copies of your personal information may remain stored on our systems even after the deletion of the information or the termination of your account.

#### Security

Your Faves account is password-protected. We take reasonable precautions to protect our Users' information, use industry standard measures to protect information that is stored within our database and limit the access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function.

#### Emails and Opt-out

Registered Users may opt-out of Faves initiated email by clicking "Email Settings" under the "My Account" link and following the instructions therein. Registered users cannot currently opt-out of peer-initiated email. 

The only Faves email sent to Unregistered Users is peer-initiated. Unregistered Users may opt-out of peer-initiated email by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of a received email. 

#### Contacting Our Web Site

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at:

Blue Dot, Inc.  
811 First Avenue, Suite 480  
Seattle, WA 98104
